You know, Chandler, you're doing so well with this whole getting married, never
你知道，錢德勒，你在整個結婚過程中做得很好，從來沒有
going to sleep with anyone for the rest of your life thing.
下半輩子就和誰睡這件事。
I'm telling you, I think it's great.
我告訴你，我認為這很棒。
Hey.
嘿。
Hi.
你好。
Who wants French toast?
誰想要法式吐司？
Oh, I'll have some.
哦，我要一些。
Me too.
我也是。
Eggs and milk in the fridge, thanks.
雞蛋和牛奶放在冰箱裡，謝謝。
Oh, what's the matter, honey?
噢，怎麼了，親愛的？
Oh, my hand feels weird.
哦，我的手感覺很奇怪。
I guess it's because I'm engaged.
我想這是因為我訂婚了。
Oh.
哦。
How long before that starts getting annoying?
多久之後就會開始變得煩人？
Starts?
開始？
Yeah, so let's actually get started on the wedding plans.
是的，讓我們開始製定婚禮計劃。
Okay.
好的。
Already?
已經？
Yeah, we got a lot to do.
是的，我們還有很多事要做。
We gotta think about the flowers, the caterers, the music.
我們必須考慮鮮花、餐飲服務和音樂。
Oh, I got some thoughts on the music.
哦，我對音樂有一些想法。
Oh, Chandler, too many cooks.
哦，錢德勒，廚師太多了。
Take it from me, as the groom, all you have to do is
聽我說，身為新郎，你要做的就是
show up and try to say the right name.
出現並嘗試說出正確的名字。
Okay.
好的。
What in God's name is that?
天啊那是什麼？
Oh, my God, the wedding book?
天哪，結婚書？
I haven't seen that since the fourth grade.
從四年級開始我就沒見過這樣的事了。
This baby has got everything.
這個嬰兒已經擁有了一切。
Take, you know, locations, for instance.
以地點為例。
First organized alphabetically, then geographically, then by square footage.
首先按字母順序排列，然後按地理排列，最後按平方英尺排列。
That is so smart.
那真是太聰明瞭。
Break it off.
打破它。
Break it off now.
現在就斷掉吧。
Oh, my, look, here's the invitation you used to your wedding to John
哦，天哪，看，這是你和約翰結婚時用的邀請函
Lynch in the fifth grade.
林奇五年級。
Remember, I got sick and Ross had to fill in as a bridesmaid.
請記住，我生病了，羅斯不得不擔任伴娘。
I was a bridesboy.
我是一名伴娘。
I don't smell French toast, bridesboy.
我沒有聞到法式吐司的味道，伴郎。
But you're always stuck in second gear.
但你總是被困在二檔。
When it hasn't been your day or week or month or year.
當這不是你的一天、一週、一個月或一年的時候。
But I'll be there for you, baby.
但我會在你身邊，寶貝。
And that should conclusively prove that I had the idea for Jurassic Park
這應該最終證明我有侏羅紀公園的想法
first.
第一的。
I need to talk to you.
我需要和你談談。
It's pretty urgent.
事情相當緊急。
It's about Monica and Chandler.
這是關於莫妮卡和錢德勒的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Of course.
當然。
Would you please excuse me for a moment?
請您原諒一下好嗎？
Do you know each other's hometowns?
你們知道彼此的家鄉嗎？
Why don't you...
你為什麼不...
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
Well, not much, but I was just thinking that since those guys just
嗯，不多，但我只是在想，既然那些傢伙只是
got engaged, that maybe it'd be nice if they had some privacy, you
訂婚了，如果他們有一些隱私也許會很好，你
know?
知道？
So, could I just move in with you for a couple days?
那麼，我可以搬去跟你住幾天嗎？
Um, okay.
嗯，好吧。
Yeah, sure.
是的，當然。
But what's wrong with Monica and Chandler?
但莫妮卡和錢德勒怎麼了？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
Why?
為什麼？
Phoebe, you said it was urgent.
菲比，你說事情很緊急。
Oh, yeah, it is.
哦，是的，是的。
I'm going to the movies and it starts in like five minutes.
我要去看電影，電影大約五分鐘後就開始了。
Do you realize I have a classroom full of students?
你知道我的教室裡擠滿了學生嗎？
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦，對不起。
I'm so rude.
我太粗魯了。
Does anyone want to come to the movies?
有人想來看電影嗎？
All right, so I haven't cleared the budget with my parents yet, but
好吧，所以我還沒跟父母搞清楚預算，但是
tell me how this is for music.
告訴我這對音樂來說怎麼樣。
Okay.
好的。
All right.
A string quartet for the processional, a jazz trio for cocktails, the Bay
遊行弦樂四重奏、雞尾酒爵士三重奏、海灣
City Rollers for dancing.
跳舞的城市滾軸。
Wait, that was for my sixth-grade man.
等等，那是給我六年級的同學的。
Well, you couldn't get them anyway.
好吧，無論如何你都無法得到它們。
I mean, Ian doesn't even play anymore.
我的意思是，伊恩甚至不再打球了。
And Derek.
還有德里克。
Well, Derek is a name I shouldn't know.
好吧，德瑞克是一個我不應該知道的名字。
Hey, Mom, do you have another pillow?
嘿，媽媽，你還有另一個枕頭嗎？
You know, something a little snugglier?
你知道，更舒服一點的東西嗎？
Why are you napping over here instead of over at your place?
為什麼在這裡打盹而不是在你那裡打瞌睡？
The duck.
鴨子。
What?
什麼？
The duck?
鴨子？
What the hell did the damn duck do now?
該死的鴨子現在到底做了什麼？
Uh, well, he did not get sick somewhere in there, and it was
呃，好吧，他並沒有在那裡的某個地方生病，而且是
immediately found and properly cleaned up.
立即發現並妥善清理。
Now, do I get to look at this book, or is it just
現在，我該看這本書嗎，還是隻是
for people who are actually involved in the wedding?
對於真正參與婚禮的人？
Of course you can look at it.
當然你可以看看。
Yeah, I want your opinion, too.
是的，我也想聽聽你的意見。
Okay.
好的。
Here you go.
幹得好。
What do you think about centerpieces?
您對中心裝飾品有何看法？
Centerpieces.
中心裝飾品。
Yeah.
是的。
Roses or lilies?
玫瑰還是百合？
Definitely roses.
絕對是玫瑰。
Well, I just think they're a little bit more wedding-y, you know.
嗯，我只是覺得它們更像婚禮，你知道。
But lilies are the clear choice.
但百合是明智的選擇。
Oh, I get it.
哦，我明白了。
It's like one mind.
就好像一心一意一樣。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Guys, guys, you gotta let me nap.
夥計們，夥計們，你們得讓我睡一會兒。
I'm gonna get cranky.
我會變得暴躁。
Joey, there is a perfectly good couch across the hall.
喬伊，大廳對面有一張非常好的沙發。
Yes, it is perfectly good, and it is not one of the places
是的，非常好，而且不是其中之一
the duck got sick.
鴨子生病了。
What?
什麼？
All right, I'm gonna go.
好吧，我要走了。
Joey, what did the duck do?
喬伊，鴨子做了什麼？
I don't know, but he did not eat your face cream.
我不知道，但他沒有吃你的乳霜。
Hey, little buddy.
嘿，小夥伴。
How you feeling?
你感覺怎麼樣？
What the hell is in that face cream?
那個乳霜裡面到底是什麼？
That's so soft.
真是太軟了。
Pillowcases.
枕頭套。
Zelda looked at the chimney sweep.
薩爾達看著掃煙囪的人。
Her father, the vicar, vicar.
她的父親，牧師，牧師。
Yeah.
是的。
Wouldn't be home for hours.
幾個小時都不會回家。
Her loins were burning.
她的腰部在燃燒。
She threw caution to the wind and reached out and grabbed his...
她不顧一切，伸手抓住了他的…
Whoa!
哇！
This is a dirty book!
這是一本骯髒的書！
Hey.
嘿。
Uh, Phoebe.
呃，菲比。
Oh, Ross.
哦，羅斯。
Hi.
你好。
Phoebe, what are you doing?
菲比，你在做什麼？
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I'm with a client right now.
我現在正在和一個客戶在一起。
Phoebe!
菲比！
Okay, let's talk outside.
好吧，我們去外面談談。
Joel, um, unfortunately, this time will be counted as part of your massage.
喬爾，嗯，不幸的是，這次將算是你按摩的一部分。
So, um, try and think relaxing thoughts.
所以，嗯，試著想一些放鬆的想法。
And, Joel, don't touch any of my dinosaurs.
還有，喬爾，別碰我的恐龍。
I know they're cool, but they're mine.
我知道它們很酷，但它們是我的。
Phoebe, you can't massage people in my apartment.
菲比，你不能在我的公寓裡幫別人按摩。
What's the big deal?
有什麼大不了的？
I did it at Monica and Chandler's.
我在莫妮卡和錢德勒家做的。
And they knew about it?
他們知道這件事嗎？
Okay, look, Ross, what is this really about?
好吧，羅斯，你看，這到底是關於什麼的？
Look, this is my home, and I want to be able to come
看，這是我的家，我希望能夠來
and go whenever I want.
我想什麼時候去就什麼時候去。
Okay, I will find someplace else to do the rest of my appointments.
好的，我會找其他地方完成剩下的約會。
I just don't know what the big deal is.
我只是不知道有什麼大不了的。
The big deal is I don't want naked, greasy strangers in my apartment
重要的是我不想讓裸體、油膩的陌生人出現在我的公寓裡
when I want to kick back with a puzzle.
當我想用拼圖來放鬆一下。
Beer.
啤酒。
Cold beer.
冰鎮啤酒。
Hey, Joey.
嘿，喬伊。
What you doing?
你在做什麼？
Sweeping.
掃地。
Why?
為什麼？
Does it turn you on?
它讓你興奮嗎？
No.
不。
What if I was sweeping a chimney?
如果我掃煙囪怎麼辦？
Joey, did you eat my face cream?
喬伊，你吃了我的乳霜嗎？
Where you going?
你要去哪裡？
The vicar won't be home for hours.
牧師幾個小時內不會回家。
Joey, where did you learn that word?
喬伊，你從哪裡學到這個詞的？
Where do you think?
你覺得哪裡呢？
Zelda?
薩爾達？
You found my book?
你找到我的書了嗎？
Yeah, I did.
是的，我做到了。
Joey, what are you doing going into my bedroom?
喬伊，你進我臥室做什麼？
Okay, I'm sorry.
好吧，對不起。
I went in there to take a nap.
我進去睡午覺。
And I know I shouldn't have, but you got bored.
我知道我不該這麼做，但你覺得無聊。
God, I cannot believe you invaded my privacy like that.
天哪，我不敢相信你這樣侵犯了我的隱私。
Whoa, Zelda.
哇，薩爾達。
You seem a little tense.
你看起來有點緊張。
Maybe you'd relax if I gave you a nice milk bath.
如果我幫你洗個舒服的牛奶浴，也許你會放鬆下來。
Okay.
好的。
I don't even like that part.
我甚至不喜歡那部分。
Oh, I do.
哦，我願意。
Hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道嗎？
I don't care.
我不在乎。
I'm not ashamed of my book.
我並不為我的書感到羞恥。
There's nothing wrong with a woman enjoying a little erotica.
女人享受一點色情並沒有什麼不好。
It's just a healthy expression of female sexuality, which, by the way, is
這只是女性性慾的健康表達，順便說一句，
something that you will never understand.
你永遠不會理解的東西。
You got bored.
你感到無聊了。
Oh!
哦！
Hello.
你好。
Hi.
Is Phoebe here?
菲比在嗎？
Uh, no, no.
呃，不，不。
She's out for the night.
她晚上出去了。
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
Can I help you with something?
我可以幫你做點什麼嗎？
Well, I don't know.
嗯，我不知道。
Are you a masseur?
你是按摩師嗎？
Yes, I am.
我是。
Great.
偉大的。
Dad?
爸爸？
Thank you so much.
太感謝了。
I'll be back to pick him up in an hour.
我一小時後回來接他。
You need help with that?
您需要協助嗎？
So, Chad, like, your parents must have been thrilled when you told them
所以，查德，當你告訴你的父母時，他們一定很興奮
you were engaged.
你已經訂婚了。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
I should probably call them.
我也許應該打電話給他們。
I remember when we first got engaged.
我記得我們第一次訂婚的時候。
Oh, I don't think I've ever heard that story.
哦，我想我從來沒有聽過這個故事。
Oh, Dad, really, you don't need to...
哦，爸爸，真的，你不需要...
Well, I gotten Judy pregnant.
好吧，我讓茱蒂懷孕了。
I still don't know how that happened.
我還是不知道那是怎麼發生的。
You don't know how that happened?
你不知道那是怎麼發生的？
Your dog thought my diaphragm was a chew toy.
你的狗以為我的隔膜是個咀嚼玩具。
What a sweet story.
多麼甜蜜的故事。
Well, at least you're not hearing it for the first time at your
好吧，至少你不是第一次在家裡聽到它
fifth-grade Halloween party.
五年級的萬聖節派對。
What?
什麼？
They wanted a scary story.
他們想要一個恐怖的故事。
We're really excited about our wedding plans, and I guess pretty soon we'll
我們對我們的婚禮計劃感到非常興奮，我想很快我們就會
be making a big withdrawal from the Monica Wedding Fund.
從莫妮卡婚禮基金中提取一大筆資金。
What?
什麼？
You tell her, Jack, I can't do it.
你告訴她，傑克，我做不到。
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
You still have the Monica Wedding Fund, don't you?
你還有莫妮卡婚禮基金，不是嗎？
We have it.
我們有。
Only now we call it the Beach House.
現在我們才稱之為海濱別墅。
I can't believe you spent my wedding fund on the Beach House.
我不敢相信你把我的婚禮資金花在了海濱別墅上。
We're sorry, honey, but we just assumed if you got married after you
很抱歉，親愛的，但我們只是假設你結婚後
turned 30, you'd pay for it yourself.
30歲了，你就要自己付錢了。
You bought the Beach House when I was 23.
我 23 歲時你買了海濱別墅。
Which means you had seven years of beach fun, and you can't put
這意味著你已經享受了七年的海灘樂趣，而且你不能把
a price on that, sweetie.
親愛的，這個價格。
I really do feel bad about this, though.
不過，我確實對此感到難過。
We started saving again when you were dating Richard, but then that went
當你和理查德約會時，我們又開始存錢了，但後來就這樣了
to hell, so we redid the kitchen.
天哪，所以我們重新裝修了廚房。
What about when I started dating Chandler?
那我什麼時候開始和錢德勒約會呢？
Well, it was Chandler.
嗯，是錢德勒。
We didn't think he'd ever propose.
我們沒想到他會求婚。
Clearly, I did not start drinking enough at the start of the meal.
顯然，我在用餐開始時沒有喝足夠的水。
I can't believe it.
我簡直不敢相信。
There is no money for my wedding?
我的婚禮沒錢了？
We might still have some money if your father hadn't thought it was
如果你父親沒有想到的話我們可能還有一些錢
a good idea to sell ice over the Internet.
在網路上賣冰是個好主意。
It seemed like such a simple idea.
這似乎是一個簡單的想法。
Stupid, Jack.
愚蠢的，傑克。
The word is stupid.
這個詞很愚蠢。
All right, enough.
好吧，夠了。
I don't want to hear about it anymore.
我不想再聽到這件事了。
Good luck, Chandler.
祝你好運，錢德勒。
Sorry.
對不起。
Okay.
好的。
Now I'm going to...
現在我要...
touch you.
觸控你。
Ooh.
哦。
Oh, that's soft.
噢，那是軟的。
Why does Joey
為什麼喬伊
keep talking about chimney sweeps and vicars?
一直在談論煙囪清潔工和牧師嗎？
Uh, I think he's just been rehearsing for an episode of his show.
呃，我想他剛剛在排練他的節目的一集。
Oh.
哦。
Yeah.
是的。
Because it really sounds like a bad porn novel.
因為這聽起來確實像是一部糟糕的情色小說。
I can't believe this.
我簡直不敢相信這一點。
Do you think that your parents could help pay for it?
你認為你的父母可以幫忙支付費用嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道。
My mother spent most of her money on her fourth wedding.
我母親在第四次婚禮上花了大部分錢。
She's saving the rest for her divorce.
她把剩下的錢存起來準備離婚。
And any extra cash my father has, he saves for his yearly trips
我父親有多餘的錢，他都會存起來用於每年的旅行
to...
到...
Dollywood.
多萊塢。
What happened at dinner?
晚餐時發生了什麼事？
My parents spent the money for our wedding.
我父母為我們的婚禮花了錢。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What did you order?
你點了什麼？
Wait.
等待。
There's no money?
沒錢嗎？
Well, this is terrible.
嗯，這太可怕了。
You guys are going to have to get married in, like, a rec
你們必須在一場娛樂活動中結婚
center.
中心。
God, you're right.
天哪，你是對的。
We're going to have to be out by six so, you know, they
我們必須在六點前出發，所以，你知道，他們
can take out the floor for seeing you swim.
可以把地板拿出來看你游泳。
Honey, it's going to be okay.
親愛的，一切都會好起來的。
No, no, it's not.
不，不，不是。
It's not going to be okay.
不會有事的。
It sucks.
太糟糕了。
No swing band, no lilies.
沒有鞦韆樂隊，沒有百合花。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
But that's good.
但這很好。
You don't want lilies.
你不要百合花。
If a cat ate them, it would die.
如果貓吃了它們，它就會死。
What?
什麼？
I'm just saying that now you could invite cats.
我只是說現在你可以邀請貓了。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
It's going to be okay.
一切都會好起來的。
I mean, you don't need to have this rustic Italian feast, you know,
我的意思是，你不需要吃這種質樸的義大利盛宴，你知道，
and you don't need this custom-made, empire-waisted, duchess satin gown.
而且您不需要這件訂製的高腰公爵夫人緞面禮服。
You can wear off-the-rack.
您可以直接穿著現成的。
Look, it really is going to be okay.
看吧，真的會沒事的。
The important thing is that we love each other and that we're going
重要的是我們彼此相愛並且我們會一起走下去
to get married.
結婚。
Do you even understand what off-the-rack means?
您甚至瞭解現成的意思嗎？
Why don't you just pay for it yourself?
為什麼不自己付錢呢？
How?
如何？
I don't have any money.
我沒有錢。
Well, I have some.
嗯，我有一些。
How much?
多少？
Well, close to...
嗯，接近...
Whoa!
哇！
Are you kidding me?
你在開玩笑吧？
What?
什麼？
How much is it?
多少錢？
It's enough for wedding scenario A.
對於婚禮場景A來說就足夠了。
Really?
真的嗎？
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等。
If scenario A has lilies in it, someone's going to have to break
如果場景 A 中有百合花，就必須有人打破
it to the cats and it ain't going to be me.
是給貓的，而不會是我。
How great are you, you little saver?
你這個小儲蓄者有多厲害？
I mean, the amount you have is exactly the budget of my dream
我的意思是，你擁有的金額正是我夢想的預算
wedding.
婚禮。
Oh, you guys are so made for each other.
哦，你們真是天生一對。
Well, you're not suggesting that we spend all of the money on the
好吧，你並不是建議我們把所有的錢都花在
wedding.
婚禮。
Uh, yeah.
呃，是的。
Come on, I've been saving this money for six years and I kind
拜託，我已經存了六年的錢了，我很感激
of had some of it earmarked for the future, not just for a
其中一些專門用於未來，而不僅僅是為了
party.
派對。
Wow!
哇！
Hello, Mr. Chandler.
你好，錢德勒先生。
This is the most special day of our lives.
這是我們一生中最特別的一天。
Oh, I realize that, honey, but I'm not going to spend all the
哦，我意識到了，親愛的，但我不會花掉所有的錢
money on one party.
一方的錢。
Honey, um, I love you, but, um, if you call our wedding a
親愛的，嗯，我愛你，但是，嗯，如果你稱我們的婚禮為
party one more time, you may not get invited.
再聚會一次，你可能就不會被邀請了。
Listen, we can always earn more money, okay, but we're only going to
聽著，我們總是可以賺更多的錢，好吧，但我們只會
get married once.
結婚一次。
Look, I understand, but I have to put my foot down, okay?
聽著，我明白，但我必須堅定立場，好嗎？
The answer is no.
答案是否定的。
You're, you're going to have to put your foot down?
你，你必須放下你的腳嗎？
Yes, I am.
我是。
Wow, money and a firm hand.
哇，錢和堅定的手。
Finally a Chandler I can get on board with.
終於有一個我可以加入的錢德勒了。
Hey, Ridge.
嘿，裡奇。
Joey.
喬伊。
Hey, Ridge, you smell smoke?
嘿，裡奇，你聞到煙味了嗎？
Uh-huh, I get it.
嗯嗯，我明白了。
Smoke, chimney, chimney sweep, very funny, ha-ha.
冒煙，煙囪，掃煙囪，很好笑，哈哈。
No, no, no, I'm serious.
不不不，我是認真的。
You don't smell it?
你沒聞到嗎？
Something's on fire.
有東西著火了。
No, no, I don't smell anything.
不，不，我沒有聞到任何味道。
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道嗎？
It's probably just your burning loins.
可能只是你的腰部著火了。
Hey, what are you guys, what are you guys talking about?
嘿，你們在說什麼，你們在說什麼？
Nothing.
沒有什麼。
Damn, this coffee's cold.
該死，這咖啡冷了。
Hey, Ridge, do you mind if I heat this up on your loins?
嘿，裡奇，你介意我把這個加熱到你的腰部嗎？
You know, I cannot believe you told him, Joey.
你知道，我不敢相信你告訴了他，喬伊。
So, I guess you bought that book after we broke up, huh?
所以，我猜你是在我們分手後買了那本書，對吧？
Uh-huh, yeah, I did because I wore out my first copy when
嗯嗯，是的，我這麼做是因為我的第一本已經用壞了
I was with you.
我和你在一起。
Oh, yeah, yeah, well, uh, when we were going out, I read tons
哦，是啊，是啊，嗯，呃，當我們出去的時候，我讀了很多書
of porno magazines.
色情雜誌。
Sup?
蘇普？
Ross, how could you do that to an old man?
羅斯，你怎麼能這樣對待一個老人？
Excuse me, ladies.
對不起，女士們。
I'm sorry?
對不起？
My massage client, Arthur, his daughter called and said that some guy that
我的按摩客戶亞瑟，他的女兒打電話來說，有人
worked for me gave him a really weird massage this afternoon.
為我工作的人今天下午給他做了一個非常奇怪的按摩。
I gave him an extremely professional massage.
我給他做了非常專業的按摩。
He said you poked at him with wooden spoons.
他說你用木湯匙戳他。
Okay, so it wasn't a traditional massage, but I did give him a
好吧，這不是傳統的按摩，但我確實給了他一次
little bit of acupressure with a pair of chopsticks and, and I gently
用一雙筷子一點點指壓，然後我輕輕地
exfoliated him with, with a mop.
用拖把給他去角質。
Well, he's never coming back, okay?
好吧，他永遠不會回來了，好嗎？
You just cost me $80 a week.
你每週只花了我 80 美元。
Hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道嗎？
This is your fault.
這是你的錯。
You're the one who didn't move his appointment.
你是那個沒有改變他的約會的人。
Oh, it's my fault?
哦，是我的錯嗎？
You didn't have to massage him.
你沒必要給他按摩。
You could have sent him away.
你本來可以把他送走。
You could have not rolled taco chops up and down his back.
你不可能把玉米餅排在他背上滾來滾去。
He said he liked that.
他說他喜歡這樣。
Oh, you're right.
哦，你是對的。
You're right.
你說得對。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Dude, what are you massaging an old man for?
老兄，你幫老人按摩幹什麼？
His daughter was hot.
他的女兒很熱。
Gotcha.
明白了。
Look, Ross, I really need that $80 every week.
羅斯，你看，我每週確實需要 80 美元。
Look, I am sure you'll find another massage client, Phoebe.
聽著，我相信你會找到另一個按摩客戶，菲比。
Yeah, I'm sure I will, too.
是的，我相信我也會的。
But until then, I'm going to massage you every week for the price
但在那之前，我會每週為你按摩一次
of $100.
100 美元。
You just said $80.
你剛才說的是80美元。
Do you want me to mess up your puzzle?
你想讓我把你的拼圖弄亂嗎？
A hundred it is.
是一百。
Hello, Zelda.
你好，薩爾達。
Who are you supposed to be?
你應該是誰？
The vicar.
牧師。
Do you even know what a vicar is?
你知道什麼是牧師嗎？
Like a goalie, right?
就像守門員一樣，對吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Look, Joey, it's enough, all right?
聽著，喬伊，夠了，好嗎？
The joke's over.
笑話結束了。
I'm sick of it.
我受夠了。
You mean this isn't the sweet torment you've been waiting all your life
你的意思是這不是你一輩子都在等待的甜蜜折磨
for?
為了？
Joey, I'm serious, all right?
喬伊，我是認真的，好嗎？
It's enough.
夠了。
You keep making these stupid jokes and these sleazy innuendos and it's not,
你一直在開這些愚蠢的笑話和這些下流的影射，但事實並非如此，
it's just not funny anymore.
這不再有趣了。
All right, I'm sorry.
好吧，對不起。
Rach, I'm sorry.
瑞秋，對不起。
Okay, I'm sorry.
好吧，對不起。
Now, maybe I can make it up to you by taking you roughly
現在，也許我可以帶你粗略地來彌補你
in the barn.
在穀倉裡。
All right, you know what?
好吧，你知道嗎？
That's it.
就是這樣。
You want to do it?
你想做嗎？
Let's do it.
我們開始做吧。
Huh?
啊？
Trent, I want to do it with you.
特倫特，我想和你一起做。
Been trying to fight it, but you've just said all the right things.
一直試圖與之抗爭，但你剛剛說了所有正確的話。
Uh, I did?
呃，我做到了？
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, I've been waiting so long to get on that body.
哦，我已經等了很久才登上那具屍體了。
This body?
這具身體？
Yeah, that's right.
是的，沒錯。
Come on, Joey, sex me up.
來吧，喬伊，讓我性感起來。
Yeah, you're starting to sound like the butcher's wife there in chapter seven.
是的，你聽起來就像第七章中屠夫的妻子。
Oh, come on now.
哦，現在來吧。
Don't keep me waiting.
別讓我等了。
Get those clothes off.
把那些衣服脫掉。
But I would keep that helmet on because you're in for a rough
但我會繼續戴上頭盔，因為你會遇到困難
ride.
騎。
I don't want to.
我不想。
I'm scared.
我很害怕。
Hey.
嘿。
Listen, um, I've been thinking, and it's not fair for me to ask
聽著，嗯，我一直在想，我這樣問是不公平的
you to spend all of your money on our wedding.
你把你所有的錢都花在我們的婚禮上了。
I mean, you work, you work really hard for that.
我的意思是，你工作，你為此非常努力。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, you work for that.
好吧，你為此而努力。
Look, I've thought about it, too, and I'm sorry.
你看，我也考慮過這個問題，我很抱歉。
I think we should spend all of the money on the wedding.
我認為我們應該把所有的錢都花在婚禮上。
You do?
你做？
Yeah, I'm putting my foot down.
是的，我要放下我的腳。
Yeah, look, when I proposed, I told you that I would do anything
是的，聽著，當我求婚時，我告訴過你我會做任何事
to make you happy, and if having the perfect wedding makes you happy,
讓你開心，如果一場完美的婚禮讓你開心，
then, then that's what we're gonna do.
那麼，那就是我們要做的事。
You're so sweet.
你真可愛。
Oh, but we, what about our, what about the future and stuff?
哦，但是我們，我們的，未來之類的呢？
Ah, forget about the future and stuff.
啊，忘記未來之類的吧。
So we only have two kids, you know?
所以我們只有兩個孩子，你知道嗎？
We'll pick our favorite and that one will get to go to college.
我們會選出我們最喜歡的一個，然後那個就可以上大學了。
You thought about that?
你想過嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
How many kids are we gonna have?
我們要生幾個孩子？
Uh, four.
呃，四個。
A boy, twin girls, and another boy.
一個男孩，一對雙胞胎女孩，還有一個男孩。
What else did you think about?
你還想到了什麼？
Well, stuff like where we'd live, you know, like a small place outside
嗯，像我們住的地方，你知道，就像外面的一個小地方
the city where our kids could learn to ride their bikes and stuff.
我們的孩子可以在這座城市學習騎腳踏車之類的東西。
You know, we could have a cat that had a bell on its
你知道，我們可以養一隻身上有鈴鐺的貓
collar and we could hear it every time it ran through the little
項圈，每次它穿過小衣領時我們都能聽到它的聲音
kitty door.
小貓門。
Of course, we'd have an apartment over the garage where Joey could grow
當然，我們在車庫上方有一套公寓，喬伊可以在那裡成長
old.
老的。
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I don't, I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
我不，我不想要一場盛大、華麗的婚禮。
Sure you do.
當然可以。
No.
不。
I want everything that you just said.
我想要你剛才說的一切。
I want a marriage.
我想要結婚。
You sure?
你確定嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
I love you so much.
我真的很愛你。
I love you.
我愛你。
Hey, listen, when you were talking about our future, you said cat, but
嘿，聽著，當你談論我們的未來時，你說的是貓，但是
you meant dog, right?
你說的是狗吧？
Yeah, totally.
是的，完全可以。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
Room temperature okay?
室溫還好嗎？
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Excellent.
出色的。
Is the music too loud?
音樂太大聲了嗎？
No.
不。
Good.
好的。
Oh!
哦！
What the hell are you doing?
你到底在做什麼？
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦，對不起。
Were you expecting a traditional massage with the hands?
您期待傳統的手工按摩嗎？
Fine.
美好的。
Now just try to relax.
現在試著放鬆一下。